Yo!
What kind of monster have you left yourself become?
How many women are still out there on your farm?
Your bare hands don't let you joke there!
Your dark collection grows back feeling
Your cold heart stays forever broken
Coffee's not telling lies
Take you really kill your wife
Porto really not worth it
Pickled in from all the highs
Kiss off death and homicides
Coffee's not telling lies
Take you really kill your wife
Porto really not worth it
Pickled in from all the highs
Kiss off death and homicides
Throw it on your wife until she follows that full level
But you make sure there was no happy ever after
And you still somewhere in your home with all the others
Cowfully preserved, floating blood
Strange bodies, bodies, bodies
프로stusch, Sakura
all these sides of this and all these sides
kiss off this and all these sides